Jeffrey Meijer

PROFILE

Jeffrey Meijer, 28 years from the Netherlands. Residing in Bali, Indonesia for the past 4 years. Active in the Real estate industry for more than 3 years.

With a background in construction and a passion for property, I enjoy guiding clients in the progress of searching or creating their new property.

I'm social, hardworking, result-oriented driven and I love good teamwork.

SKILLS

- Communication
- CRM
- IT (Systems/Microsoft Office)
- · Construction and development
- · Property regulations
- Area knowledge

DETAIL KONTAK

- (+31)641975206 (+62)81994415265
- 🗯 Gang Nirwana no.6, Kerobokan. Bali
- in @Thejeffmeijer

LANGUAGES

Eng

Dutch - Fluent

English - Fluent

Indonesian - Basic



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Exclusive

Invest Islands - June 2021 - Present

Handle incoming leads and assist with inquiries by responding to phone calls, emails, and text messages. Provide potential clients with information about our Investments, legal structure and give presentations while creating a sustainable relationship with the clients.

Consultant Real Estate & Investments

Freelance - December 2020 - Present

Give advice and guidance to clients for purchasing real estate in Indonesia with my main focus on the Dutch Market.

Real Estate Agent

Villas of Bali - December 2019 - December 2020

Handle incoming inquiries for potential clients that are looking for short-term or long-term accommodation in Bali. Guiding them through the process from A till Z. Doing on-site inspections, making contracts, preparing financial payments and solving tax related issues.

Founder - Directeur

Meijer Renovation - August 2016 - December 2019

EDUCATION

Media & IT Management

ID The Netherlands